<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Islamic App</string>
    <string name="rules_amp_methods"><![CDATA[RULES & METHODS]]></string>
    <string name="txtwh">
        <br>Wudu is required before praying salah. The steps must be completed in the given
order below, and they must be done without long pauses between each of the steps.

</br>
    </string>
    <string name="step1">
     <n><br><b>  Steps:- </b></br></n>
       <b> <br>1.</br></b>  <br>	 Make niyyah (intention) to perform wudu, and say "Bismillah" (in the name of Allah) before starting wudu.</br>
                                           <br></br>
                                           <br> •	Niyyah is the Islamic concept of performing an act for the sake of Allah. To truly perform wudu, you should center yourself and quiet your thoughts, focusing seriously on what you are doing (intending to perform wudu (ablution)). </br>
                                                     <br></br>
                                      <n>      <br> •	Niyyah is not said out loud and should be made in the heart; focusing on the phrase "Bismillah" (in the name of Allah) is a good way to accomplish the necessary centering. Say it out loud or silently to yourself, whichever makes you comfortable.</br> </n>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>

    </string>
    <string name="step2">
         <b> <br>2.</br></b> <br>Wash your hands. Use your left hand to wash your right hand. Do this three times. After that, use your right hand to wash your left hand three times. Make sure to wash in between your fingers and all the way up to your wrists.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step3"><b> <br>3.</br></b> <br>	Take water into your mouth. Use your right hand to cup water into your mouth three times. Swish it around in your cheeks. Do this thoroughly.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step4"><b> <br>4.</br></b> <br>	Inhale water into your nose. Use your right hand to cup water and inhale it into your nose and blow out three times. Snort sharply and abruptly without taking too much water into your nose and choking yourself. If you cannot inhale water into your nose, you can wet your fingers and put water on the lower part of your nostrils.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step5"><b> <br>5.</br></b> <br>	Wash your face. Wash your face three times by spreading your hands from your right ear to the left, and from the hairline to the chin.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step6"><b> <br>6.</br></b> <br>	Wash your lower arms from wrists to elbows, leaving no part dry. From your wrist to your elbow, wash your right arm with your left hand three times and then wash your left arm with your right hand three times</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step7"><b> <br>7.</br></b> <br>	Clean your head. This is known as "maseh". Using your wet hands, gently wipe the entire head once, from the forehead to the back of the head, and wipe it again forward from the back of the head to the forehead.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step8"><b> <br>8.</br></b> <br>	Wipe your ears inside and out. Use your thumb to clean behind your ears from the bottom upward. This is also done one time.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step9"><b> <br>9.</br></b> <br>	Wash both of your feet. Clean up to the ankles and be sure water goes between the toes. Use your pinky finger and go through each toe to eliminate anything between. Start with your right foot and scrub each foot three times.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="step10"><b> <br>10.</br></b> <br> Finish your wudu with the dua - Ash-hadu ’an laa ’ilaaha ’illallaahu wahdahu laa shareeka lah, wa ’ash-hadu ’anna Muhammadan ’abduhu wa Rasooluh.</br>
                                               <br> I bear witness that none has the right to be worshipped but Allah alone, Who has no partner; and I bear witness that Muhammad is His slave and His Messenger.</br>
                                                     <br></br>
                                                         <br>•	Memorize the order. Wudu should be performed one after another   (Tarthib), so it is important that you know the order of the steps so that you can follow them accurately.</br>
                                                     <br></br>
                                                         <br>•	If you make a mistake in the order, you must begin your wudu from the beginning again.</br>
        <br></br><br></br><br></br>
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_dua">dua</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="duaen">Duaen</string>
    <string name="gps_settings_title" />
    <string name="gps_settings_text" />
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="location">Detect location</string>
    <string name="madina">Madina</string>
    <string name="fajr">Fajr</string>
    <string name="dohr">Dhor</string>
    <string name="asr">Asr</string>
    <string name="maghrib">Magrib</string>
    <string name="isha">Isha</string>
    <string name="menu_prayertimes">Salah Times</string>
    <string name="menu_prayersettings">Prayer settings</string>
    <string name="ok" />
    <string name="cancel" />
    <string name="gpsplz" />
    <string name="consignes" />
    <string name="qibladirection" />
    <string name="fromnorth" />
    <string name="qiblatips" />
    <string name="permission_not_garanted" />
    <string name="coord" />
    <string name="latitude" />
    <string name="locationunready" />
    <string name="longitude" />

    <string name="manualcorr" />

    <string name="minutes"></string>
    <string name="locationloading" />
    <string name="internetfound">Data renewing process</string>
    <string name="internetlost">To refresh the page, you must be connected to the Internet</string>
    <string name="hello" />
    <string name="firstalertdialogmsg">We thank you for downloading this application, do not forget to share it with loved ones and take the initiative to recite, dhikr and good deeds</string>

    <string name="clickbackagaintoexit">Press again to exit the application</string>
    <string name="errorloadprayertimes">Faulty renewal of prayer times</string>


    <string name="menu_fadl1">It is one of the best simple righteous deeds that bring a Muslim closer to his Lord, the Glorious and the Exalted.</string>
    <string name="menu_fadl2">Some verses and hadiths on the merit of dhikr, supplication and urging them:</string>
    <string name="menu_fadlGod1">Allah says :</string>
    <string name="menu_fadlGod2">And the Almighty said:</string>
    <string name="menu_fadlProphet">And the Messenger of God, may God bless him and grant him peace, said:</string>
    <string name="ProphetSaid">The prophet Peace Be Upon Him said:</string>
    <string name="thought1" translatable="false">"وَلَذِكْرُ اللَّهِ أَكْبَرُ".</string>
    <string name="thought2" translatable="false">"وَسَبِّحُوهُ بُكْرَةً وَأَصِيلًا".</string>
    <string name="thought3" translatable="false">"فَاذْكُرُونِي أَذْكُرْكُمْ وَاشْكُرُوا لِي وَلا تَكْفُرُونِ".</string>
    <string name="thought4" translatable="false">"يَا أَيُّهَا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا اذْكُرُوا اللَّهَ ذِكْراً كَثِيراً".</string>
    <string name="thought5" translatable="false"> "وَالذَّاكِرِينَ اللَّهَ كَثِيراً وَالذَّاكِرَاتِ أَعَدَّ اللَّهُ لَهُمْ مَغْفِرَةً وَأَجْراً عَظِيماً".</string>
    <string name="thought6" translatable="false">"وَاذْكُر رَّبَّكَ كَثِيرًا وَسَبِّحْ بِالْعَشِيِّ وَالْإِبْكَارِ".</string>
    <string name="thought7" translatable="false">"الَّذِينَ يَذْكُرُونَ اللَّهَ قِيَامًا وَقُعُودًا وَعَلَىٰ جُنُوبِهِمْ".</string>
    <string name="thought8" translatable="false">"فَإِذَا قَضَيْتُم مَّنَاسِكَكُمْ فَاذْكُرُوا اللَّهَ كَذِكْرِكُمْ آبَاءَكُمْ أَوْ أَشَدَّ ذِكْرًا".</string>
    <string name="thought9" translatable="false">"يَا أَيُّهَا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا لَا تُلْهِكُمْ أَمْوَالُكُمْ وَلَا أَوْلَادُكُمْ عَن ذِكْرِ اللَّهِ".</string>
    <string name="thought10" translatable="false"> "وَاذْكُرْ رَبَّكَ فِي نَفْسِكَ تَضَرُّعاً وَخِيفَةً وَدُونَ الْجَهْرِ مِنْ الْقَوْلِ بِالْغُدُوِّ وَالآصَالِ وَلا تَكُنْ مِنْ الْغَافِلِينَ".</string>
    <string name="thought11" translatable="false">" مثل الذي يذكر ربه و الذي لا يذكر ربه مثل الحي و الميت."</string>
    <string name="thought12" translatable="false">ألا أنبئكم بخير أعمالكم و أزكاها عند مليككم و أرفعها في درجاتكم و خير لكم من أنفاق الذهب و الورق و خير لكم من أن تلقوا عدوكم فتضربوا أعناقهم و يضربوا أعناقكم ?، قالو بلى .  قال : (ذكر الله تعالى).</string>
    <string name="thought13" translatable="false">يقول الله تعالى : أنا عند ظن عبدي بي ، و أنا معه إذا ذكرني ، فان ذكرني في نفسه ذكرته في نفسي و ان ذكرني في ملأ ذكرته في ملأ خير منهم ، و ان تقرب إلي شبرا تقربت اليه ذراعا و ان تقرب إلى ذراعا تقربت اليه باعا و ان اتاني يمشي أتيته هرولة.</string>
    <string name="thought14" translatable="false">من قعد مقعدا لم يذكر الله فيه كانت عليه من الله تره ، و من أضطجع مضجعا لم يذكر فيه الله كانت عليه ترة.</string>
    <string name="thought15" translatable="false">ما جلس قوم مجلسا لم يذكروا الله فيه ، و لم يصلوا على نبيهم الا كان عليهم ترة فان شاء عذبهم و ان شاء غفر لهم.</string>
    <string name="thought16" translatable="false">" ما من قوم يقومون من مجلس لا يذكرون الله فيه الا قاموا عن مثل جيفة حمار و كان لهم حسره."</string>
    <string name="prayertimesloaded">Prayer times have been updated</string>


    <string name="AdkarExtra1">The adhkaar illuminates the servant his path in his world and in the afterlife and on the straight path</string>
    <string name="AdkarExtra2">The dhikr works to cleanse the tongue and distract it from backbiting, gossip and spoiled saying</string>
    <string name="AdkarExtra3">The dhikr brings mercy, tranquility, comfort and security to the Muslim and envelops him with angels</string>
    <string name="AdkarExtra4">Remembrance of God Almighty is equivalent to the best deeds of freeing people and striving for the sake of God Almighty, and spending money for His</string>
    <string name="AdkarExtra5">The morning and evening remembrances relax the heart and spread reassurance and psychological comfort in the Muslim’s heart</string>
    <string name="AdkarExtra6">The morning and evening remembrance help the Muslim to avoid negligence from the remembrance of God</string>
    <string name="SalatThought1" translatable="false">َالَّذِينَ هُمْ عَلَى صَلَاتِهِمْ يُحَافِظُونَ*أُولَئِكَ فِي جَنَّاتٍ مُّكْرَمُونَ</string>
    <string name="SalatThought2" translatable="false">إِنَّ الصَّلاةَ كَانَتْ عَلَى الْمُؤْمِنِينَ كِتَاباً مَوْقُوتاً</string>
    <string name="SalatThought3" translatable="false">وَأَنْ أَقِيمُوا الصَّلَاةَ وَاتَّقُوهُ وَهُوَ الَّذِي إِلَيْهِ تُحْشَرُونَِ</string>
    <string name="SalatThought4" translatable="false">يَا أَيُّهَا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا اسْتَعِينُوا بِالصَّبْرِ وَالصَّلَاةِ إِنَّ اللَّهَ مَعَ الصَّابِرِينَ</string>
    <string name="SalatThought5" translatable="false">وَأَقِمِ الصَّلَاةَ طَرَفَيِ النَّهَارِ وَزُلَفًا مِنَ اللَّيْلِ إِنَّ الْحَسَنَاتِ يُذْهِبْنَ السَّيِّئَاتِ ذَلِكَ ذِكْرَى لِلذَّاكِرِينَ</string>
    <string name="SalatThought6" translatable="false">يَا أَيُّهَا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا ارْكَعُوا وَاسْجُدُوا وَاعْبُدُوا رَبَّكُمْ وَافْعَلُوا الْخَيْرَ لَعَلَّكُمْ تُفْلِحُونَ</string>
    <string name="SalatThought7" translatable="false">إِنَّ الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ وَأَقَامُوا الصَّلَاةَ وَآتَوُا الزَّكَاةَ لَهُمْ أَجْرُهُمْ عِنْدَ رَبِّهِمْ وَلَا خَوْفٌ عَلَيْهِمْ وَلَا هُمْ يَحْزَنُونَ</string>
    <string name="SalatExtra1">Prayer is the first to be held accountable on the Day of Resurrection. Its righteousness is good for his deeds, and its corruption is corruption for his deeds</string>
    <string name="SalatExtra2">Maintaining the prayer on time for one of the most beloved works of God Almighty</string>
    <string name="SalatExtra3">Prayer is a light, guidance and pilgrimage to its owner in this world and the hereafter when meeting God Almighty</string>
    <string name="SalatExtra4">Prayer is a light for its owner in this world and in the hereafter</string>
    <string name="SalatExtra5">Prayer is the best deeds for God Almighty after the two Shahada</string>
    <string name="itsprayertime">Prayer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_arabic_quran">arabic_quran</string>


    <string name="d2d_dua1">\nبِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمَنِ الرَّحِيْم\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Bismil laahir Rahmaanir Raheem\n\nTranslation – “Al’laah’s Name we begin with, The Compassionate, Most Merciful.”</string>
    <string name="d2d_dua2">\nاَلْحَمْدُ للهِ الَّذِىْ اَطْعَمَنَا وَسَقَاناَ وَجَعَلَناَ مِنَ الْمُسْلِمِيْنَ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Alhumdu lil laahil Lazee At’amana Wa Saqaana Wa Ja’alana Minal Muslimeen”.\n\nTranslation – “All Praise is due to Al’laah, who has blessed us with food and drink and made us from amongst the Believers (Muslims)”.</string>
    <string name="d2d_dua3">\nاللّهُـمَّ افْتَـحْ لي أَبْوابَ رَحْمَتـِك\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Allaahum-maf-Tahlee Abwaaba Rahmatika”.\n\nTranslation – “O Allaah, open the doors of Your Mercy for me.” </string>
    <string name="d2d_dua4">\nاللّهُـمَّ إِنّـي أَسْأَلُكَ مِـنْ فَضْـلِك\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Allaahum-ma In-nee As`aluka Min Fadhlika”.\n\nTranslation – “O Allaah, I seek of You Your Grace.” </string>
    <string name="d2d_dua5">\nالْحَمْدُ لِلَّ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Alhamdulillah”!\n\nTranslation – “Thanks and all praise be to Allah”
                            \nيَرْحَمُكَ اللَّهُ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Yar Hamoo kall Lah”.\n\nTranslation – “May Allah have mercy on you.”</string>
    <string name="d2d_dua6">\nبِسْـمِ اللهِ وَلَجْنـا، وَبِسْـمِ اللهِ خَـرَجْنـا، وَعَلـى رَبِّنـا تَوَكّلْـنا\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Bismillaahi walajnaa, wa bismillaahi kharajnaa, wa ‘alaaRabblnaa tawakkalnaa”\n\nTranslation – “In the Name of Allah we enter, in the Name of Allah we leave, and upon our Lord we depend [then say As-Salaamu ‘Alaykum to those present]."</string>
    <string name="d2d_dua7">\بِسْمِ اللهِ تَوَكَّلْتُ عَلىَ اللهِ وَلاَ حَوْلَ وَلاَ قُوَّةَ اِلاَّ بِاللهِ ط\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Bismil laahi Tawak’kaltu Alal laahi Wa Laa Hawla Wa Laa Quw’wata il’la bil’laah“\n\nTranslation – “Al’laah’s Name we begin with, I place my (full) trust in Al’laah and there is no Might and Power except with Al’laah.”</string>
    <string name="d2d_dua8">\nسُبْحَنَ الَّذِىْ سَخَّرَلَنَا هَذَا وَ مَا كُنَّا لَهُ مُقْرِنِيْنْ وَ اِنَّا اِلَى رَبِّنَا لَمُنْقَلِبُوْنْ\nِ
        \nTransliteration –“Subhaanal lazee Sakh’khara Lana Haaza Wa Maa Kun’na Lahu Muqrineen. Wa In’na ilaa Rab’bina La Munqaliboon”.\n\nTranslation –  “Glory be to Al’laah who has given us control over this (mode of transport) and without his Grace we would not have been able to control it and undoubtedly we are to return towards our Lord.”</string>


    <string name="prayer_dua1">\nأَسْتَغْفِرُ اللَّهَ.(ثَلاثاً) اللَّهُمَّ أَنْتَ السَّلاَمُ، وَمِنْكَ السَّلَامُ، تَبَارَكْتَ يَا ذَا الْجَلَالِ وَالإِكْرَامِ.\nِ
        \nTransliteration – "Astaghfirul-lah (three times) Allahumma antas-salam waminkas-salam, tabarakta ya thal-jalali wal-ikram."\n\nTranslation – "I ask Allah for forgiveness.(three times) O Allah, You are As-Salam and from You is all peace, blessed are You, O Possessor of majesty and honour.’ AS-Salam: The One Who is free from all defects and deficiencies."</string>
    <string name="prayer_dua2">\nلَا إلَهَ إِلاَّ اللَّهُ وَحْدَهُ لَا شَرِيكَ لَهُ، لَهُ الْمُلْكُ وَلَهُ الْحَمْدُ وَهُوَ عَلَى كُلِّ شَيْءٍ قَدِيرٌ، اللَّهُمَّ لَا مَانِعَ لِمَا أَعْطَيْتَ، وَلَا مُعْطِيَ لِمَا مَنَعْتَ، وَلَا يَنْفَعُ ذَا الْجَدِّ مِنْكَ الْجَدُّ.َ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “La ilaha illal-lahu wahdahu la shareeka lah, lahul-mulku walahul-hamd, wahuwa AAala kulli shayin qadeer, allahumma la maniAAa lima aAAtayt, wala muAAtiya lima manaAAt, wala yanfaAAu thal-jaddi minkal-jad.”.\n\nTranslation – “None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise and He is over all things omnipotent.O Allah, none can prevent what You have willed to bestow and none can bestow what You have willed to prevent, and no wealth or majesty can benefit anyone, as from You is all wealth and majesty.”.</string>
    <string name="prayer_dua3">\nسُبْحَانَ اللَّهِ، وَالْحَمْدُ لِلَّهِ، وَاللَّهُ أَكْبَرُ. (ثلاثاً وثلاثين) لَا إِلَهَ إِلاَّ اللَّهُ وَحْدَهُ لَا شَرِيكَ لَهُ، لَهُ الْمُلْكُ وَلَهُ الْحَمْدُ وَهُوَ عَلَى كُلِّ شَيْءٍ قَدِيرٌ.\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Subhanal-lah walhamdu lillah, wallahu akbar (thirty-three times). La ilaha illal-lahu wahdahu la shareeka lah, lahul-mulku walahul-hamd, wahuwa AAala kulli shayin qadeer.”.\n\nTranslation – “How perfect Allah is, all praise is for Allah, and Allah is the greatest.’ (thirty-three times) None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise and He is over all things omnipotent.” </string>
    <string name="prayer_dua4">\nقُلْ هُوَ اللهُ أَحَدٌ. اللهُ الصَّمَدُ. لَمْ يَلِدْ وَلَمْ يُولَدْ. وَلَمْ يَكُنْ لَهُ كُفُوًا أَحَدٌ. [ الإِخْـلاصْ ] قُلْ أَعُوذُ بِرَبِّ الْفَلَقِ. مِنْ شَرِّ مَا خَلَقَ. وَمِنْ شَرِّ غَاسِقٍ إِذَا وَقَبَ. وَمِنْ شَرِّ النَّفَّاثَاتِ فِي الْعُقَدِ. وَمِنْ شَرِّ حَاسِدٍ إِذَا حَسَدَ [ الفَلَـقْ ] قُلْ أَعُوذُ بِرَبِّ النَّاسِ. مَلِكِ النَّاسِ. إِلَهِ النَّاسِ. مِنْ شَرِّ الْوَسْوَاسِ الْخَنَّاسِ. الَّذِي يُوَسْوِسُ فِي صُدُورِ النَّاسِ. مِنَ الْجِنَّةِ وَالنَّاسِ [ الـنّاس ] (ثلاث مرات بعد صلاتي الفجر والمغرب. ومرة بعد الصلوات الأخرى)\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Qul Huwa-llahu ‘Ahad\nAllahus-Samad\nLam Yalid Wa Lam Yulad\nWalam Yakul-La-Hu-Kufuwan ‘Ahad [Al-Ikhlas] Qul ‘A’udhu Bi-Rabbil-Falaq\nMin Sharri Ma Khalaq\nWa Min Sharri Ghasiqin ‘Idha Waqab\nWa Min Sharri-Naffathati Fil-‘Uqadi\nWa Min Sharri Hasidin ‘Idha Hasad [Al-Falaq] Qul ‘A’udhu Bi-Rabbin-Nas\nMalikin-Nas\nIlahin-Nas\nMin-Sharril-Waswasil-Khan-Nas\nAl-Ladhi Yuwas-wisu Fee Sudurin-Nas\nMina Al-Jinnati Wan-Nas [An-Nas]”.\n\nTranslation – “Say : He is Allah,(the) One, Allahus-Samad ( The Self-Sufficient Master, Whom all creatures need, He neither eats nor drinks ). He begots not , nor was He begotten; And there is none co-equal or comparable unto Him. [Al-Ikhlas] Say : I seek refuge with ( Allah ) the Lord of the daybreak, From the evil of what He has created; And from the evil of the darkening ( night ) as it comes with its darkness; ( or the moon as it sets or goes away ). And from the evil of the witchcrafts when they blow in the knots, And from the evil of the envier when he envies. [Al-Falaq] Say : I seek refuge with (Allah ) the lord of mankind, The king of mankind, The Ilah ( God ) of mankind, From the evil of the whisperer ( devi l who whispers evil in the hearts of men) , who withdraws ( from his whispering in one’s heart after one remembers Allah ), Who whispers in the breasts of mankind , Of jinns and men. [An-Nas] After morning and evening prayers, 3 times. After the other prayers 1 time.” </string>
    <string name="prayer_dua5">\nاللَّهُ لاَ إِلَهَ إِلاَّ هُوَ الْحَيُّ الْقَيُّومُ لاَ تَأْخُذُهُ سِنَةٌ وَلاَ نَوْمٌ لَّهُ مَا فِي السَّمَاوَاتِ وَمَا فِي الأَرْضِ مَن ذَا الَّذِي يَشْفَعُ عِنْدَهُ إِلاَّ بِإِذْنِهِ يَعْلَمُ مَا بَيْنَ أَيْدِيهِمْ وَمَا خَلْفَهُمْ وَلاَ يُحِيطُونَ بِشَىْءٍ مِّنْ عِلْمِهِ إِلاَّ بِمَا شَاءَ وَسِعَ كُرْسِيُّهُ السَّمَاوَاتِ وَالأَرْضَ وَلاَ يَؤُودُهُ حِفْظُهُمَا وَهُوَ الْعَلِيُّ الْعَظِيمَُّ\nِ
        </string>
    <string name="prayer_dua6">\nلَا إِلَهَ إِلَّا اللَّهُ وَحَدْهُ لَا شَرِيكَ لَهُ، لَهُ الْمُلْكُ وَلَهُ الْحَمْدُ يُحْيِي وَيُمِيتُ وَهُوَ عَلَى كُلِّ شَيْءٍ قَدِيرٌ . (عَشْر مَرّات بَعْدَ المَغْرِب وَالصّـبْح )\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “La ilaha illal-lahu wahdahu la shareeka lah, lahul-mulku walahul-hamd, yuhyee wayumeet, wahuwa AAala kulli shayin qadeer.(ten times after the maghrib &amp; fajr prayers)”\n\nTranslation – “None has the right to be worshipped except Allah, alone, without partner, to Him belongs all sovereignty and praise, He gives life and causes death and He is over all things omnipotent. (ten times after the maghrib and fajr prayers)"</string>
    <string name="prayer_dua7">\اللَّهُمَّ إِنِّي أَسْأَلُكَ عِلْماً نَافِعاً وَرِزْقاً طَيِّباً، وَعَمَلاً مُتَقَبَّلاً . (بَعْد السّلامِ من صَلاةِ الفَجْر )\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Allahumma innee as-aluka AAilman nafiAAan, warizqan tayyiban, waAAamalan mutaqabbalan.(after salam from fajr prayer).“\n\nTranslation – “O Allah, I ask You for knowledge which is beneficial and sustenance which is good, and deeds which are acceptable. (To be said after giving salam for the fajr prayer)”</string>


    <string name="health_more_dua1">\nاللّهُـمَّ عافِـني في بَدَنـي ، اللّهُـمَّ عافِـني في سَمْـعي ، اللّهُـمَّ عافِـني في بَصَـري ، لا إلهَ إلاّ أَنْـتَ. اللّهُـمَّ إِنّـي أَعـوذُبِكَ مِنَ الْكُـفر ، وَالفَـقْر ، وَأَعـوذُبِكَ مِنْ عَذابِ القَـبْر ، لا إلهَ إلاّ أَنْـتَ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Allaahumma aafinee fee badanee, Allaahumma aafinee fee sam ee, Allaahumma aafinee fee basaree, laa ilaaha illaa Anta. Allaahumma innee a oothu bika minal-kufri, walfaqri, wa a oothu bika min athaabil-qabri, laa ilaaha illaa Anta."\n\nTranslation – “O Allah, make me healthy in my body. O Allah, preserve for me my hearing. O Allah, preserve for me my sight. There is none worthy of worship but You . O Allah , I seek refuge in You from disbelief and poverty and I seek refuge in You from the punishment of the grave . There is none worthy of worship but You.”</string>
    <string name="health_more_dua2">\nاللَّهُمَّ ربَّ النَّاسِ ، أَذْهِب الْبَأسَ ، واشْفِ ، أَنْتَ الشَّافي لا شِفَاءَ إِلاَّ شِفَاؤُكَ ، شِفاءً لا يُغَادِرُ سقَماً\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Allahumma Rabban-naas, azhibil-ba’s, washfi antash-Shaafi laa shifaa’a illaa shifaa’uka, shifaa’an laa yughaadiru saqamaa”.\n\nTranslation – “O Allah, Lord of mankind, do away with my suffering. Heal (me) as You are the only Healer and there is no cure except that of Yours, it is that which leaves no ailment behind”.</string>
    <string name="health_more_dua3">\nلَا بَأْسَ طَهُورٌ إِنْ شَاءَ اللَّهُ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Laa ba sa tahoorun inshaa Allaah.”\n\nTranslation – “Do not worry, it will be a purification (for you), Allah willing.” </string>
    <string name="health_more_dua4">\nأَعُوذُ بِكلِمَاتِ الله التّامّاتِ مِن شَرّ مَا خَلَقَ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “A’uzu bikalimatillahit-tammaati min syarri ma kholak”.\n\nTranslation – “I seek protection in the perfect words of Allah from every evil that has been created” </string>
    <string name="health_more_dua5">\nاللَّهُمَّ إِنِّي أَعُوذُ بِكَ مِنَ الْبَرَصِ، وَالْجُنُونِ، وَالْجُذَامِ، وَمِنْ سَيِّئِ الأَسْقَامِ\nِ
        \nTransliteration – “Allahumma inni a’uzubika minal baros, wal junuun wal juzam, wa min sayyi’-il-asqam”\n\nTranslation – “O Allah, I seek refuge in You from leprosy, madness, elephantiasis, and evil diseases”</string>
</resources>